Viewers all over the world, wherever you are,
whatever medium you are using to watch this channel,
distance is not a barrier.
You have received the Word of God.
I pray the Word finds a place in your heart, in Jesus Christ's name.
I can't hear you.
[Amen.]
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
When we feed on the Word, it makes our way plain before us.
Feeding on the Word makes our way plain before us.
Constantly pray in your heart in hymns, in spiritual songs, making melodies in your heart to the Lord.
As for me, I meditate on the Word day and night and whatever I do, prospers.
I meditate on the Word day and night and whatever I do, prospers.
Viewers all over the world,
millions of prayers are prayed with almost no faith - only faith pleases God
Have faith in God
All things are possible
Millions of prayers are prayed with almost no faith.
Right now - heart to heart.
I command all spirits from your past that are hindering your present and future
to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
Viewers, I command all spirits from your past that are hindering your present and future
to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Spirit of poverty, hardship, hatred, rejection, stagnation - leave, in the name of Jesus!
Where can we go from His presence?
Spirit of poverty - leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Spirit of affliction - leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Stagnation, rejection, isolation - leave you, in the name of Jesus!
They must leave you.
At the command of Jesus, Peter walked on the sea.
At the command of Jesus, Blind Bartimaeus regained his sight.
At the command of Jesus, the storm stood still.
At the command of Jesus, I command them to leave you, in the name of Jesus!
Leave my people!
They must leave!
Spirit of poverty must leave!
Spirit of sickness, affliction, stagnation, joblessness, barrenness - leave my people!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
You must leave - you devil, you must leave!
At the command of Jesus, Peter walked on the sea.
"Come!" He commanded.
At the command of Jesus, Blind Bartimaeus said, "Son of David, have mercy on me!"
He regained his sight.
At the command of Jesus, the storm stood still.
Let there be calm!
In your business - let there be calm!
In your career - let there be calm!
Let there be calm!
In my business - let there be calm!
In my career - let there be calm!
In my marriage - let there be calm!
In my family - let there be calm!
Let there be calm!
In my future - let there be calm!
In my nation - let there be calm!
In my country - let there be calm!
In Jesus' name!
Pray Along With Prophet T.B. Joshua
Touch Your Screen By Faith In Jesus' Name
I can hear breakthrough in your business.
I can hear breakthrough in your family.
I can hear breakthrough in your finances.
I can hear breakthrough, in Jesus Christ's name!
Let someone rejoice!
TT: Vi Czmut
RV: Mel Flowers 25/11/2018